Personal detail ★ Colombian ★ 965-0005

Aizu-Wakamatsu, Japan, Nali heights No. 203 Wakanishi 213-5, Kamega, Ikki machi

+81 80 7897 1182 arevaloarboled@

hotmail.com, gmail.com m5231113@

u-aizu.ac.jp

(7) Git

C/C++/C#

RIIRV

in Linkedin

arevaloarboled

ArevaloCamilo

uan Camilo Arévalo Arboleda

Curriculum Vitae

Rersonal profile

I have a bachelor in computer science with experience in animation, interactive systems, and web-oriented computation. I am mainly interested in music information retrieval, speech recognition, web back-end development, VR development, software development, machine learning, and data mining. I am disciplined, proactive, responsible, acquisitive and with excellent analytic skills. I stand out for excellent performance in programming code.

Education

Currently – 04/2019 Master Student in Computer Science

Research topic: Sound spatialisation

GPA 4.0/4.0

11/2018 - 07/2012 **Bachelor of Computer Science** Pontifical Xavierian University Cali

Cum Laude, GPA 3.81/5

Program with ABET international accreditation

</> Programming **JAVASCRIPT**

.ΙΔ\/Δ

PYTHON

OpenCV

NodeJS

Docker

LISP

PHP

Experience

Currently - 04/2019 Teacher Assistant

Assist in the practical and theoretical lectures of computer science undergrad-

University of Aizu

University of Aizu

uate courses. Sush as: Virtual reality, Sound and audio processing and C++ programming. Tasks: preparing material, solve doubts and grading exercise.

12/2018 - 06/2018

Research Assistant Pontifical Xavierian University Cali

Built an online game "Tramas: parques intercultural," as a didactic tool to promote the intercultural dialogue.

Internship

University Complutense of Madrid

Researched and implemented a tracking map for artworks of artistic heritage value during the Spanish civil war and the postwar.

08/2016 - 06/2016Years of experience

11/2018

Research Assistant

Pontifical Xavierian University Cali Developed an digital representation of Spanish pieces of art for historical re-

search.

12/2014 - 08/2014

Research Assistant

Pontifical Xavierian University Cali

Researched, designed, and implemented an algorithm capable of finding

salsa song choruses for the construction of a data set.

Frameworks and tools **Pure Data**

SQL

Unity **MATLAB** Arduino

Publications

Accurate Spatialization of VR Sound Sources in the Near Field.

Boostrap & [Undergraduate thesis] **AngularJS** OpenMPI/OpenMP

Camilo Arévalo, Gerardo M. Sarria M., Julián Villegas.

AES Int. Con. on Spatial Reproduction - Aesthetics and Science (Tokyo, Japan) 2018.

QQ Developing a Narrative Database for Spanish Art Starting from the End.

A.A. Navarro Newball, I. Moreno Sánchez, B. Barinaga López, D.F. Loaiza, L.S. Osorio, F.D. Paredes, J. C. Arévalo, S. Juri, E.M. Amézquita, V.E. Contreras.

12th Colombian Conference on Computing (12CCC), Cali, Colombia 2017.

(Native) Towards an Efficient Algorithm to Get the Chorus of a Salsa Song. (Fluent) Camilo Arévalo, Garardo M. Sarria M. Mario Mora Carlos Aread and Carlos Are

Camilo Arévalo, Gerardo M. Sarria M., Mario Mora, Carlos Arce-Lopera.

IEEE International Symposium on Multimedia (ISM2015), Miami, FL, USA 2015.

Spanish English

Az Languages

Japanese (Conversational)

OS Preference

GNU/Linux Windows **MacOS**

April 3, 2020



Honors & awards

3rd prize in Expo poster REDIS South West Node 2018

Research graduation contest held by 21 undergraduate Computer Science programs insti-

Ranked 8th in the ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) South

America / North Regional 2016 Member of "CodeBreakers" team

2015 Ranked 20th in the ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) South America / North Regional 2015

Member of "CodeBreakers" team

2014 Honorable mention in the ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) South America / North Regional 2014

Member of "CodeBreakers" team

2013 Ranked 24th in the ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest (ICPC) South America / North Regional 2013

Member of "CodeBreakers" team

